[{"question": "\u0427\u0442\u043e \u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0435 Python?", "options": ["\u042f\u0437\u044b\u043a \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0433\u0440\u0430\u043c\u043c\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u0438\u044f", "\u0422\u0438\u043f \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445", "\u041c\u0443\u0437\u044b\u043a\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u0438\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442", "\u0417\u043c\u0435\u044f \u043d\u0430 \u0430\u043d\u0433\u043b\u0438\u0439\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043c"], "correct_option": 0}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u0442\u0438\u043f \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0438\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0446\u0435\u043b\u044b\u0445 \u0447\u0438\u0441\u0435\u043b?", "options": ["int", "float", "str", "natural"], "correct_option": 0}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u0442\u0438\u043f \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0438\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0447\u0438\u0441\u0435\u043b c \u043f\u043b\u0430\u0432\u0443\u044e\u0449\u0435\u0439 \u0442\u043e\u0447\u043a\u043e\u0439?", "options": ["int", "float", "str", "natural"], "correct_option": 1}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u0442\u0438\u043f \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0438\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0442\u0435\u043a\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0445 \u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u043a?", "options": ["int", "float", "str", "natural"], "correct_option": 2}, {"question": "\u0427\u0442\u043e \u0438\u0437 \u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0447\u0438\u0441\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0433\u043e \u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043b\u0438\u0448\u043d\u0438\u043c?", "options": ["if()", "for()", "while()", "do while()"], "correct_option": 0}, {"question": "\u0427\u0442\u043e \u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0442\u0438\u043f\u043e\u043c \u043a\u043e\u043d\u0442\u0435\u0439\u043d\u0435\u0440\u0430 \u0438\u0437 Python?", "options": ["array", "List", "Vector", "\u0412\u0441\u0435 \u0432\u044b\u0448\u0435 \u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0447\u0438\u0441\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0435"], "correct_option": 1}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u0438\u0435 \u0431\u0438\u0431\u043b\u0438\u043e\u0442\u0435\u043a\u0438 \u043c\u044b \u043d\u0435 \u0438\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043b\u0438 \u043d\u0430 \u043a\u0443\u0440\u0441\u0435?", "options": ["NumPy", "Pandas", "Keras", "OS"], "correct_option": 2}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0435 \u0438\u0437 \u043f\u0440\u0438\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0451\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u043e\u0431\u044a\u044f\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0439 \u0444\u0443\u043d\u043a\u0446\u0438\u0439 \u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u043c?", "options": ["int a:", "define a():", "Function a():", "def a():"], "correct_option": 3}, {"question": "\u0412 \u043a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043c \u0433\u043e\u0434\u0443 \u0431\u044b\u043b \u0441\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0430\u043d Python?", "options": ["1991", "2007", "1987", "1994"], "correct_option": 0}, {"question": "\u041a\u0442\u043e \u0441\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0430\u043b Python?", "options": ["\u0413\u0432\u0438\u0434\u043e \u0432\u0430\u043d \u0420\u043e\u0441\u0441\u0443\u043c", "\u0414\u0435\u043d\u043d\u0438\u0441 \u0420\u0438\u0442\u0447\u0438", "\u0411\u044c\u0451\u0440\u043d \u0421\u0442\u0440\u0430\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u043f", "\u0411\u0440\u0435\u043d\u0434\u0430\u043d \u0410\u0439\u043a"], "correct_option": 0}]